Oh, I want to tell you how much I love you.
That you're the boy whom I love most.
Oh, he stole my heart.
That boy stole my heart.
Oh, I want to tell you how much I love you.
That you're the boy whom I love most.
That you're the boy
When my eyelid lifts
And you're close by,
I feel that I don't want to leave my side.
The day and the night are your realm.
You are the golden boy.
I want you to always be soaked in me.
You're completely bound up
With the beautiful, the most lovely, with the adorned.
Stay lying down here a little longer.
Because I want to use you as a pillow.
I want to draw on you without taking advantage.
I want to seek you in me and seek myself in you.
And when we find each other, both of us, within us,
I want to please you in me and please myself in you.
Oh, I want to tell you how much I love you.
That you're the boy whom I love most.
That you're the boy
My soul would be disarmed if at the end of the day
It were not made complete by your stay.
Forgive me if one day I doubted.
But doubt is what urges
The heart to break with the structure.
The fear of feeling cracks
For which it's hard to find the cure.
But it's madness to fear what might happen
And stop doing what one would wish.
What I know that I desire
Is to fill myself with your company.
Because you're what inspires me.
Because with you life is more.
You add to me, you expand me, you make me more capable.
For that and for much, much, much more.
Oh, I want to tell you how much I love you.
That you're the boy whom I love most.
That you're the boy
Oh, he stole my heart.
That boy stole my heart.
And if my ribs beat,
It's because I love you.
And if my knees tremble,
And if miles separate us,
I still love you.
Despite millions of miles,
This is over.